securef5.com 2015-03-21

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
   v.6 — 06-01-2011

At ComF5, LLC. ("comF5®" or "Service Provider"), we respect our Users'
and Clients' right to privacy with regards to the use of their email and our
Web sites. We have adopted a privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") that we
hope provides the greatest possible privacy to our Users and Clients,
assuming they are not using our services to conduct unlawful activities.
Our Privacy Policy makes the following commitments:
WE WILL NOT USE CLIENT OR USER INFORMATION FOR ANY
PURPOSES OTHER THAN TO PROVIDE THE BEST POSSIBLE
HOSTED EMAIL, EMAIL MARKETING, ON DEMAND STREAMING
MEDIA AND RELATED SERVICES. MORE SPECIFICALLY, WE WILL
NOT SHARE USER OR CLIENT INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES
IN WAYS OTHER THAN DISCLOSED IN THIS POLICY. ADDITIONALLY,
WE WILL NOT EMPLOY TECHNOLOGY TO READ EMAIL MESSAGES
IN ORDER TO TARGET, DISPLAY OR SEND MARKETING ADS BASED
ON THE CONTENT OF THOSE EMAIL MESSAGES.
This Privacy Policy discloses the types of personal information collected
and stored by Service Provider and how that information is used to provide
the email services and related sales and support services ("Email
Services"). Client acknowledges and agrees to the collection and use of its
personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.
Website Information
Service Provider collects statistical information about how people ("Users")
locate and navigate its Web sites. This information, sent by normal Web
browsers, usually includes the browser type, Internet Protocol (IP) address
and referring URL. This information is used to improve the usefulness of
the Web sites and to enhance the positioning of Web sites within Internet
search engines. Users remain anonymous unless they voluntarily contact
Service Provider by filling out an online form, at which point this data may
be linked with Users in order to provide the best possible service.
                                                                                 comF5®
                                                        7469 W. Lake Mead Blvd. Suite 100
                                                                    Las Vegas, NV 89128
                                                                     Phone: 702.938.9300
                                                                       Fax: 888.566.3314
                                                                  Email: info@comF5.com
                                                                   Web: www.comF5.com

Demonstration Email Accounts
Web site Users may request a fully functional demo account by filling out
an online form. This form requires a valid email address and phone
number so that Service Provider can contact User by email or phone to
confirm potential fit of the email solution and to provide User with the demo
account password. Service Provider does not use submitted demo request
form data for any purpose other than to contact Users regarding the demo.
Contact Information
When Users fill out an online form to contact Service Provider, Service
Provider collects some personal information, including but not limited to
name, company name, phone number, email address, and reason for
contact. This information is used to respond to the customer's initial
contact in a timely manner.
Affiliate Information
When Users fill out an online form to apply for the Service Provider's
affiliate program, Service Provider collects some personal information,
including but not limited to name, company name, title, phone number,
address, email address and tax ID number. This information is used to
help Service Provider determine whether or not Users qualify for entry into
the program.
Cookies
A cookie is a small piece of information that a Web server can store
temporarily with a Web browser. Cookies are useful for having a browser
remember specific information that the Web server can later retrieve.
When Users visit Service Provider owned Web sites, a cookie is set on
their browser for the purpose of gathering statistical data about how the
Service Provider Web sites are being used. The use of cookies improves
                                                                                  comF5®
                                                         7469 W. Lake Mead Blvd. Suite 100
                                                                     Las Vegas, NV 89128
                                                                      Phone: 702.938.9300
                                                                        Fax: 888.566.3314
                                                                   Email: info@comF5.com
                                                                    Web: www.comF5.com

the quality of the Web sites, however if Users prefer, they may configure
their browser not to accept cookies. Web browsers that do not accept
cookies will still be able to access some of the Service Provider sites.
Cookies are tied to Users' personal information only when a purchase is
made, a demo is requested, or a contact form is filled out.
Third Party Cookies
Some of the businesses we advertise with use cookies on our Web site to
help us determine the effectiveness of our Web site content and
advertising. We have no control over third party cookies. This Privacy
Policy covers the use of cookies by comF5, and does not cover the use of
cookies by any advertisers. The information that these companies collect
and share through this technology is not personally identifiable. This sub-
section on Third Party Cookies only applies to the Web Site Information
section of this Privacy Policy and DOES NOT APPLY TO THE CLIENT
ACCOUNT INFORMATION section. More specifically, we do not use Third
Party Cookies when providing Email Services to Clients.
Clear Gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs)
Some of the businesses we advertise with employ a software technology
called clear gifs (i.e. Web Beacons/Web Bugs) to help us determine the
effectiveness of our Web site content and advertising. Clear gifs are tiny
graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are
used to track the online movements of Users. In contrast to cookies, which
are stored on Users' computer hard drives, clear gifs are embedded
invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of
this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our
customers' personally identifiable information. This sub-section on Clear
Gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs) only applies to the Web Site
Information section of this Privacy Policy and DOES NOT APPLY TO THE
CLIENT ACCOUNT INFORMATION section. More specifically, we do not
use Clear Gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs) when providing Services
to Clients.
                                                                                  comF5®
                                                         7469 W. Lake Mead Blvd. Suite 100
                                                                     Las Vegas, NV 89128
                                                                      Phone: 702.938.9300
                                                                        Fax: 888.566.3314
                                                                   Email: info@comF5.com
                                                                    Web: www.comF5.com

Choice/Opt-Out
Prior to signing up for our services, we collect personally identifiable
information when creating a demonstration account, when contacting our
staff, when requesting customer support and when applying for our affiliate
program. We only collect personally identifiable information that is
voluntarily submitted via our online Web site forms. WE WILL ONLY
CONTACT USERS WHEN A REQUEST FOR CONTACT OR A FULLY
FUNCTIONAL DEMO ACCOUNT HAS BEEN MADE. Users have the
option of opting out of future communications by informing the company
representative that contacts them, by emailing support@comF5.com, or by
postal mail at the address listed below.
Client and User Account Information
When people sign up and pay for Services ("Clients"), Service Provider
collects some personal information, including but not limited to name,
phone number, billing address, payment information and password. A
secret question and answer may also be asked in order to verify the
identity of Clients if their account password is lost.
Information Safeguards
WE WILL NOT USE CLIENT INFORMATION FOR ANY PURPOSES
OTHER THAN TO PROVIDE THE BEST POSSIBLE HOSTED EMAIL,
EMAIL MARKETING, ON DEMAND STREAMING MEDIA AND RELATED
SERVICES. MORE SPECIFICALLY, WE WILL NOT SHARE CLIENT
INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES IN WAYS OTHER THAN
DISCLOSED IN THIS POLICY. ADDITIONALLY, WE WILL NOT EMPLOY
TECHNOLOGY TO READ EMAIL MESSAGES IN ORDER TO TARGET,
DISPLAY OR SEND MARKETING ADS BASED ON THE CONTENT OF
THOSE EMAIL MESSAGES.
                                                                                comF5®
                                                       7469 W. Lake Mead Blvd. Suite 100
                                                                   Las Vegas, NV 89128
                                                                    Phone: 702.938.9300
                                                                      Fax: 888.566.3314
                                                                 Email: info@comF5.com
                                                                  Web: www.comF5.com

Support Information
When Clients fill out an online form to make a request for customer
support, Service Provider collects some personal information, including but
not limited to name, company name, phone number, email address,
domain name and description of the inquiry. This information is used to
open a trouble ticket so that Service Provider can remedy the issue as
quickly as possible.
Cookies. When Clients use Service Provider comF5 services, a cookie is
set on their browser for security authentication purposes. Client sensitive
information IS NOT stored within these cookies, unless Clients specifically
select the "Remember my info" check box on the comF5 login page
located at www.comF5.com. If Clients prefer, they may configure their
browser not to accept cookies. When browsers are configured not to
accept cookies, Email Services will still be available via POP3 and IMAP4
standard protocols, however, for security reasons the comF5 applications
will not be available.
Email Contents
The contents of Clients' email accounts are stored on Service Provider
servers in order to provide the Email Services. This information is stored
on secure servers, which process the information in order to provide
Clients with authenticated access to their mailbox receive and transmit
email messages and prevent unsolicited bulk email ("Spam"). Email
contents are backed up to separate storage systems daily for the purpose
of recovery from errors or system failure. Copies of email messages may
remain on the backup storage systems for approximately two (2) weeks,
even after Clients delete the emails from their mailbox or after termination
of Email Services. Service Provider employees do not access the content
of any mailboxes unless Clients specifically request them to do so (e.g.,
when Clients report difficulties using their account), or if required to do so
by law, or if Service Provider in good faith believes that such action is
                                                                                 comF5®
                                                        7469 W. Lake Mead Blvd. Suite 100
                                                                    Las Vegas, NV 89128
                                                                     Phone: 702.938.9300
                                                                       Fax: 888.566.3314
                                                                  Email: info@comF5.com
                                                                   Web: www.comF5.com

necessary to protect, maintain and defend the rights and property of
Service Provider, its Clients or the public.
Special Email Addresses
All domains on the Internet are required to have a "postmaster" and
"abuse" mailbox pursuant to certain industry regulations, specifically RFC
2821 and RFC 2142. To help Clients comply with this regulation, Service
Provider automatically accepts mail for the following addresses within all
domains hosted on the Service Provider Network:
abuse@example.com - delivers to abuse@comF5.us
postmaster@example.com - delivers to root@example.com
root@example.com - delivers to an unmonitored mailbox
These special email addresses must always exist, however Clients may
request to have these addresses forward to alternate mailboxes within
their domain. Service Provider employees monitor the emails that arrive to
abuse@comF5.com solely for the purpose of following up on abuse related
complaints from Internet users and ISPs.
Log Information
Clients are provided with detailed usage statistics regarding their Email,
Email Marketing and Streaming Services. To provide this information, and
to facilitate troubleshooting of problems, Service Provider collects certain
information relating to the usage of the Services. This information is stored
in server logs and includes, but is not limited to, usage of SMTP, POP3,
IMAP, comF5, AttainMail, Spam Filtering and Virus Scanning. This
information is also aggregated in order to generate system wide usage
totals, which are used to effectively scale the system infrastructure and
improve the quality of the Services.
                                                                                 comF5®
                                                        7469 W. Lake Mead Blvd. Suite 100
                                                                    Las Vegas, NV 89128
                                                                     Phone: 702.938.9300
                                                                       Fax: 888.566.3314
                                                                  Email: info@comF5.com
                                                                   Web: www.comF5.com

Agents
We use an outside credit card processing company to bill Clients for
Services. These companies do not retain share, store or use personally
identifiable information for any other purposes. These third parties are
prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other
purpose.
Business Transitions
In the event that Service Provider goes through a business transition, such
as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of
its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the
assets transferred. You will be notified via email as well as through a
prominent notice on our Web site and control panel of any such change in
ownership or control of your personal information for at least thirty (30)
days.
Access to Personally Identifiable Information
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer
desire our Services, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate your
account in our control panel, by emailing support@comF5.com, by calling
or by postal mail at the address listed below.
Security
Service Provider has put in place physical, electronic and managerial
procedures to safeguard the information that is collected. Various security
technologies have been implemented to ensure that external parties
cannot access or modify Clients' personal information on the Service
Provider Network. Specifically, Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption is
used on specific Web pages to safeguard online purchase transactions.
SSL technology is the industry standard protocol for secure, Web-based
                                                                                  comF5®
                                                         7469 W. Lake Mead Blvd. Suite 100
                                                                     Las Vegas, NV 89128
                                                                      Phone: 702.938.9300
                                                                        Fax: 888.566.3314
                                                                   Email: info@comF5.com
                                                                    Web: www.comF5.com

communications. SSL is used by e-commerce Web sites on the Internet to
enable secure transactions between customers and suppliers. A limited
number of employees are authorized to access Clients' information when
the need to do so arises, and those employees undergo thorough
background checks and are trained on the importance of maintaining
Clients' privacy.
Children's Privacy
comF5 is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we
encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's
online activities and interests. comF5 does not knowingly collect
information from children under the age of 13 and does not target its Web
sites or Services to children under the age of 13.
Release of Personal Information in Extraordinary
Circumstances
Except as provided for in this Privacy Policy, Service Provider will never
share Clients' personal information with third parties without Clients'
express permission unless extraordinary circumstances apply. With
respect to the release of personal information, extraordinary circumstances
may exist when the disclosure of such information is legally required or
requested by a governmental entity, or when Service Provider, acting in
good faith, believes that the disclosure of such information is necessary to
conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process, protect the
rights of Service Provider, prevent a crime or protect national security, or
protect the personal safety of its Clients or the public.
Privacy Policy Changes
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to
this Privacy Policy, our Web site, and other places we deem appropriate so
that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and
                                                                                  comF5®
                                                         7469 W. Lake Mead Blvd. Suite 100
                                                                     Las Vegas, NV 89128
                                                                      Phone: 702.938.9300
                                                                        Fax: 888.566.3314
                                                                   Email: info@comF5.com
                                                                    Web: www.comF5.com

under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to
modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we
make material changes to this Policy, we will notify you here, by email, or
by means of a notice on our home page.
We value your opinions and feedback. If you have comments or questions
about our Privacy Policy, please email HQ@comF5.com or send them to:
ComF5, LLC.
7469 West Lake Mead
Las Vegas, NV 89128
                                                                               comF5®
                                                      7469 W. Lake Mead Blvd. Suite 100
                                                                  Las Vegas, NV 89128
                                                                   Phone: 702.938.9300
                                                                     Fax: 888.566.3314
                                                                Email: info@comF5.com
                                                                 Web: www.comF5.com
